<?xml version="1.0"?>

<tables>
  
  <table>
    <title>where is the ethernet cable?</title>
    <date>April 17th, 2026</date>
    <data>its been so long since last ive seen my ethernet cable lost to this monster, to the school behind the slaughter</data>
    <link>https://youtu.be/PMMty4EDANk?si=rph99-J3a4EGNB-i</link>
    <linkname>i just woke up man</linkname>
  </table>

  <table>
    <title>New flavour of buttons</title>
    <date>April 12th, 2026</date>
    <data>theres a new type of button that recreates the og news button thats usually in the Wii U eShop if u get what I mean..</data>
    <link>https://reeshop.pages.dev/news/</link>
    <linkname>Check out new ui stuffs</linkname>
  </table>

	<table>
		<title>reeShop down</title>
		<date>April 10th, 2026</date>
		<data>reeShop is down for who knows how long, and i have a hunch thats its coming from a certain ethernet cable.</data>
		<link>https://discord.gg/R275GaJSkz</link>
		<linkname>Join the reeShop Discord for updates</linkname>
	</table>
	
	<table>
		<title>News page added to website</title>
		<date>April 9th, 2026</date>
		<data>Lil' thing cannedfart made while bored, no genuinely i haven't done anything for the website in a month, also the inclusion of a footer which includes a yt channel link and discord and actual navigation, and some changes to make the website look better.</data>
		<link>https://reeshop.pages.dev/</link>
		<linkname>reeShop website, i couldn't think of a better link</linkname>
	</table>
	
	<table>
		<title>reeShop Discord is back!</title>
		<date>April 6th, 2026</date>
		<data>The reeShop Discord has been nuked on april 6th, 2026, everything was gone. But thanks to the admins and mods all the channels were restored, but the messages were not. Thanks sabisa.</data>
		<link>https://discord.gg/R275GaJSkz</link>
		<linkname>Join the reeShop Discord for updates</linkname>
	</table>
	
	<table>
		<title>reeShop is back in development</title>
		<date>April 5th, 2026</date>
		<data>Finally after who knows how long, reeShop is back in development and some stuff is happening behind the scenes. Come back in a few months and watch out to see if reeShop came out!</data>
		<link>https://discord.gg/R275GaJSkz</link>
		<linkname>Join the reeShop Discord for updates</linkname>
	</table>

	<table>
		<title>Absolutely nothing has been going on.</title>
		<date>March 20th, 2026</date>
		<data>Absolutely nothing has happened in reeShop for the past 20 days. cannedfart tried to learn python but doesn't understand SOAP ;)</data>
		<link>https://discord.gg/R275GaJSkz</link>
		<linkname>Join the reeShop Discord for updates</linkname>
	</table>

	<table>
		<title>New Policy</title>
		<date>Feb 25th, 2026</date>
		<data>Policy was added to the website, you are forced to go through it (even if you dont read it) to download the inkay patches.</data>
		<link>https://reeshop.pages.dev/policy</link>
		<linkname>View the new policy</linkname>
	</table>
	
</tables>
